
export const data = [
  {
    question: "What should you do when approaching a yellow traffic light?",
    options: ["Speed up and cross the intersection quickly", "Come to a complete stop", "Slow down and prepare to stop", "Ignore the light and continue driving"],
    correct_option: "Slow down and prepare to stop"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a red octagonal sign indicate?",
    options: ["Yield right of way", "Stop and proceed when safe", "Merge with traffic", "No left turn allowed"],
    correct_option: "Stop and proceed when safe"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a crosswalk?",
    options: ["A designated area for parking", "A place to stop and rest", "A path for pedestrians to cross the road", "A location for U-turns"],
    correct_option: "A path for pedestrians to cross the road"
  }, {
    question: "What should you do when approaching a yellow traffic light?",
    options: ["Speed up and cross the intersection quickly", "Come to a complete stop", "Slow down and prepare to stop", "Ignore the light and continue driving"],
    correct_option: "Slow down and prepare to stop"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a red octagonal sign indicate?",
    options: ["Yield right of way", "Stop and proceed when safe", "Merge with traffic", "No left turn allowed"],
    correct_option: "Stop and proceed when safe"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a crosswalk?",
    options: ["A designated area for parking", "A place to stop and rest", "A path for pedestrians to cross the road", "A location for U-turns"],
    correct_option: "A path for pedestrians to cross the road"
  }
]


export const programmingLanguagesAndFrameworks =
  [
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is commonly used for Android app development?",
      "options": ["Java", "Swift", "Kotlin", "Python"],
      "correct_option": "Java"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary language used for iOS app development?",
      "options": ["Objective-C", "Kotlin", "Swift", "C++"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which framework allows you to build cross-platform mobile apps?",
      "options": ["Xamarin", "React Native", "Flutter", "SwiftUI"],
      "correct_option": "React Native"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the core language for building apps with React Native?",
      "options": ["Java", "JavaScript", "Swift", "C#"],
      "correct_option": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is used for building native iOS apps?",
      "options": ["Java", "Swift", "Kotlin", "Objective-C"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "What language is commonly used for server-side development of mobile apps?",
      "options": ["Python", "PHP", "Ruby", "Node.js"],
      "correct_option": "Node.js"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is not natively supported by Android for app development?",
      "options": ["Java", "C++", "Kotlin", "Swift"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which framework is primarily used for building user interfaces in Android apps?",
      "options": ["SwiftUI", "UIKit", "Flutter", "React Native"],
      "correct_option": "UIKit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary programming language for building macOS apps?",
      "options": ["Swift", "Objective-C", "Kotlin", "C#"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which framework is developed by Google for building web apps and mobile apps?",
      "options": ["Xamarin", "React Native", "Angular", "Flutter"],
      "correct_option": "Angular"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is primarily used for building Windows Phone apps?",
      "options": ["C#", "Objective-C", "Java", "Swift"],
      "correct_option": "C#"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary programming language for building watchOS apps?",
      "options": ["Swift", "Objective-C", "Kotlin", "Java"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is commonly used for building games in Unity?",
      "options": ["C#", "Java", "Python", "Swift"],
      "correct_option": "C#"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary language for building web apps?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Python", "Ruby", "Java"],
      "correct_option": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is commonly used for building native Windows apps?",
      "options": ["Swift", "Java", "C#", "Objective-C"],
      "correct_option": "C#"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the core language for building apps with Flutter?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Swift", "Kotlin", "Dart"],
      "correct_option": "Dart"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is commonly used for building server-side applications?",
      "options": ["Java", "Python", "Ruby", "C#"],
      "correct_option": "Java"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary language for building backend services in Firebase?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Java", "Swift", "Python"],
      "correct_option": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which framework is used for building machine learning models in TensorFlow?",
      "options": ["Keras", "PyTorch", "Caffe", "Scikit-learn"],
      "correct_option": "Keras"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary programming language for building ARKit apps?",
      "options": ["Swift", "Java", "Objective-C", "C#"],
      "correct_option": "Swift"
    }
  ]

  export const appDeploymentandDistribution= [
    {
      "question": "What is the process of publishing an Android app on Google Play called?",
      "options": ["Submission", "Deployment", "Distribution", "Release"],
      "correct_option": "Release"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you distribute beta versions of iOS apps to testers?",
      "options": ["Via Google Play", "TestFlight", "App Store Connect", "Crashlytics"],
      "correct_option": "TestFlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an APK, and how is it related to Android app distribution?",
      "options": ["App Kit Programming", "Application Package", "Android Package Kit", "App Publishing Kit"],
      "correct_option": "Android Package Kit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the main steps to release an app on the Apple App Store?",
      "options": ["Alpha Testing, Beta Testing, Production", "Development, Testing, Production", "Submission, Review, Release", "Design, Coding, Testing"],
      "correct_option": "Submission, Review, Release"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which of the following app stores can you distribute Windows Phone apps?",
      "options": ["Google Play", "Mac App Store", "Windows Store", "App Store Connect"],
      "correct_option": "Windows Store"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a bundle identifier (Bundle ID) used for in iOS app distribution?",
      "options": ["Identifying device models", "Identifying app version", "Identifying app categories", "Uniquely identifying apps"],
      "correct_option": "Uniquely identifying apps"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of a release track (e.g., Alpha, Beta) in app distribution?",
      "options": ["To organize app assets", "To manage user reviews", "To track revenue", "To control app updates"],
      "correct_option": "To control app updates"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the minimum age requirement for a user to have a Google Play account?",
      "options": ["16", "18", "21", "There's no age requirement"],
      "correct_option": "None of these. (A Google Play account requires the user to be at least 13 years old.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of app content is typically not allowed on major app stores?",
      "options": ["Paid apps", "Educational apps", "Gambling apps", "Dating apps"],
      "correct_option": "Gambling apps"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main purpose of an app description on an app store?",
      "options": ["Showcase screenshots", "Attract potential users", "Provide customer support", "Optimize app performance"],
      "correct_option": "Attract potential users"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an A/B testing (split testing) in the context of app distribution?",
      "options": ["Testing app stability", "Testing different app versions", "Testing server performance", "Testing payment gateways"],
      "correct_option": "Testing different app versions"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which store feature allows users to preview an app without installing it?",
      "options": ["Quick View", "Instant App", "App Preview", "Try Before You Buy"],
      "correct_option": "Instant App"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary purpose of using deep links in app distribution?",
      "options": ["Track user behavior", "Improve app security", "Improve app performance", "Provide seamless user experience"],
      "correct_option": "Provide seamless user experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is app store optimization (ASO)?",
      "options": ["Optimizing app store servers", "Optimizing app development process", "Optimizing app distribution workflow", "Optimizing app listing for better visibility"],
      "correct_option": "Optimizing app listing for better visibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the typical review time for apps submitted to the Apple App Store?",
      "options": ["1 day", "1 week", "2 weeks", "It varies and can take several days"],
      "correct_option": "It varies and can take several days"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of app sandboxing on iOS?",
      "options": ["To prevent cross-platform distribution", "To prevent app crashes", "To improve app performance", "To enhance app security"],
      "correct_option": "To enhance app security"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Firebase App Distribution used for?",
      "options": ["Sending push notifications", "Monitoring app analytics", "Distributing pre-release app versions", "Managing user authentication"],
      "correct_option": "Distributing pre-release app versions"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary benefit of using app signing by Google Play?",
      "options": ["Faster app download", "Better app performance", "Enhanced app security", "Increased app revenue"],
      "correct_option": "Enhanced app security"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following app distribution methods bypasses app stores?",
      "options": ["Side-loading", "In-app purchases", "App bundles", "App previews"],
      "correct_option": "Side-loading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of setting up age ratings for an app?",
      "options": ["To target specific age groups", "To restrict user access", "To limit app downloads", "To increase app revenue"],
      "correct_option": "To target specific age groups"
    }
  ]

